[{"question": "  hey, how much will you give me to eat this whole jar of olives?", "answer": " i won\u0092t give you anything, but you\u0092ll owe me 2.95.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " done.", "answer": "  hey. i need an atlas! i need an atlas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " why?  do you have a report due?", "answer": " i have a date with this diplomat i met while i was giving free massages outside the un and, i don\u0092t know where his country is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " okay, let\u0092s start with the free messages outside the un.", "answer": " oh!! that\u0092s my new thing. i figure bodies at peace, make peace.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " wow! you might just get the first nobel prize in rubbing. so what country is this guy from?", "answer": " ick-neck-tree-anis..... there\u0092s a \u0091g\u0092 in there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " where\u0092s that?", "answer": " in your atlas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " i don\u0092t have an atlas.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " oh, but wait i do have a globe.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " hold on.", "answer": " so pheebs what\u0092s this guy like?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " umm, well he\u0092s very dashing, y'know, and umm, very, very sophisticated, and he doesn\u0092t speak any english, but according to his translator, he totally gets me.", "answer": " \u0091kay, here you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " what is this?", "answer": " it\u0092s a globe and, a pencil sharpener.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  hey, does anybody need anything copied? i\u0092m going down to the xerox place.", "answer": " oh, no thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " okay listen, just give me anything i can make two of.", "answer": " well, if you don\u0092t have anything to copy, why are you going down there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " yeah, are you just going down there to gawk at that hot girl with the belly button ring again?", "answer": " yeah! you wanna come?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " come on chloe! finish up with your customer first. come on chloe! come on chloe!!", "answer": "  can i help you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " uh-oh.", "answer": " uh, y'know what, we\u0092re having second thoughts about our copying needs. and we\u0092ll need a little more time to think about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " chloe, switch with me, there\u0092s some guys here that got a crush on you.", "answer": "  okay, that hurt us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hi guys. i haven\u0092t seen you since this morning.", "answer": " well ah, ........y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " hey, what are you guys doing tomorrow night?", "answer": " both of us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " relax. it\u0092s just issac\u0092s d.j.-ing at the philly. you should come.", "answer": " we\u0092ll be there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " great. i\u0092ll ah, see ya then.", "answer": " all right, rock on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " he\u0092s says, \u0091walking with you makes this strange city, feel like home.\u0092", "answer": " me too. although this city is my home, so. so that\u0092s dumb what i said, don\u0092t tell him i said that. umm, you make something up.  nice,  thank you. this is me. here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  your eyes are very pretty.", "answer": "  thank you, very much! oh!  thank you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "  he would like to kiss you.", "answer": "  okay, y'know what, you don\u0092t have to do that now.  no-no-no-no!! not him, you don\u0092t!  well the moment\u0092s over.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " oy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  see there it is right there.", "answer": " wow! it\u0092s small.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " yeah. but sergei said it took the germans six weeks to get all the way across it.", "answer": " so you had fun, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " yeah. except for, y'know when you\u0092re on a date and you\u0092re getting along really great but the guy\u0092s translator keeps getting in the way.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": "  hey. phoebe and monica: hey.", "answer": " what is ah, rach in her room?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh no, she\u0092s still at work, but she told me to tell you to call her.", "answer": " oh what?! is she gonna cancel on me again?! how can she do this? doesn\u0092t she know it\u0092s our anniversary?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " all right ah, ross, this is the extent of my knowledge on the subject.  call rachel.", "answer": " what\u0092s that on the bottom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  hello.", "answer": " hey, honey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " oh, hi.", "answer": " hey, what\u0092s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " well, there was a disaster in shipping and i\u0092ve got to get this order in. honey, i\u0092m so sorry, but it looks like i\u0092m gonna be here all night.", "answer": " what, do you, well umm, oh how about i come up there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  anyway, i\u0092m going out with sergei again tonight, and um, could you come and be the translator\u0092s date? so that when we, it\u0092s time for our alone time, you two could split off. y'know, he\u0092s really, he\u0092s kinda cute.", "answer": " yeah, well kinda cute, like really kinda cute, or kinda cute like your friend spackel back larry?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " hey, y'know what, maybe we should get going. i mean what time did chloe say we should be there?", "answer": " uh, 10:30.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " what time is it now?", "answer": " 4:30.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yeah all right, so we\u0092ll hang out.", "answer": " yeah. hey, remember when she brought up that thing about the three of us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yes. vividly.", "answer": " she was kidding about that right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " yeah, i-i-i think so.  yeah, i-i think so...", "answer": " god, that would be weird it that situation presented itself tonight, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " yeah. yeah, i mean what, what would we do?", "answer": " dude, i don\u0092t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " she was kidding.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " she was.... but y'know what, just in case, maybe we should come up with a set of ground rules.", "answer": " yeah, for sure. okay. probably want the first thing to be, never open your eyes. y'know, because you don\u0092t want to be doing something and then look up and see something you don\u0092t want to be seeing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " ah!! okay! eyes open at all times! oh, hey, how do we decide where we...  y'know each would,  y'know  be?", "answer": " right. right. well ah, y'know we could flip for it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " yeah, i guess, but what\u0092s like heads and what\u0092s tails?", "answer": " well it you don\u0092t know that, then i don\u0092t want to do this with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  no, no, no, i\u0092m looking at a purchase order right here and it clearly states that we ordered the rivera bikini in a variety of sizes and colours. and....  what does it matter, what i\u0092m wearing?! can i please speak to your supervisor?  thank you.  we\u0092re holding.", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  oh!! my god, what are you doing here?", "answer": " well you said you couldn\u0092t go out so....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " you brought a picnic, oh, what a boyfriend. that\u0092s it, on monday i start wearing make-up.", "answer": " ross honey, this is very nice, but, but i-i got a crisis.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " yeah, but i got cous-cous!", "answer": " honey, honey, i\u0092m sorry, i know it\u0092s our anniversary but i told you on the phone i don\u0092t have time to stop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " but i don\u0092t, hmm...  oh, who approved that order?!  well there is no mark robbinson in this office.  get me mark on the phone!", "answer": " i love mark.  do you know mark?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " yeah!!", "answer": " well, let me just check that with what i got here, all right see 038 is not the number for  this store, 038 is atlanta. and i...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  pepper?", "answer": "  none for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " okay sorry, whew.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, as i was saying the store number is wrong, and i\u0092m sorry but that\u0092s...  oh my god!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": "  okay, that\u0092s a fire. oh yeah. oh yeah.", "answer": "  excuse me, i\u0092m sorry, i\u0092m gonna have to call you back, i\u0092ve got a schemp in my office.   what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry. but ah, hey, oh, somebody\u0092s off the phone, how \u0091bout a glass of wine by the fire, i could get it going again.", "answer": " ross you\u0092re not listening to me, i don\u0092t have time to stop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " come on rach, you don\u0092t have what, ten minutes?", "answer": " i don\u0092t have ten minutes!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " what?  sophie, does she have ten minutes?", "answer": " hey, ross!!! i told you i don\u0092t!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " don\u0092t yell at me okay, this is the most i\u0092ve seen you all week.", "answer": " look, i cannot do this right now, okay, i\u0092ve got a deadline, would you just go home, i\u0092ll talk to you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " yeah, but wait...", "answer": " good bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hi. look um, about what happened earlier...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " no, hey, well, i-i completely understand. you were, you were stressed.", "answer": "  i was gonna give you a chance to apologise to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " for what? for letting you throw me out of your office?", "answer": " you had no right coming down to my office ross. you do not bring a picnic basket to somebody\u0092s work! unless maybe they were a park ranger!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " yeah, well excuse me for wanting to be with my girlfriend on our anniversary, boy what an ass am i.", "answer": " but i told you, i didn\u0092t have the time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " yeah, well you never have the time. i mean, i don\u0092t feel like i even have a girlfriend anymore, rachel.", "answer": " wh, ross what do you want from me? you want me, you want me to quit my job so you can feel like you have a girlfriend?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " no, but it\u0092d be nice if you realised, it\u0092s just a job!", "answer": " just a job!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " ross do you realise this is the first time in my life i\u0092m doing something i actually care about. this is the first time in my life i\u0092m doing something that i\u0092m actually good at. i mean. if you don\u0092t get that...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no, hey, i get that, okay, i get that big time. and i\u0092m happy for ya, but i\u0092m tired of having a relationship with your answering machine! okay, i don\u0092t know what to do anymore.", "answer": " well neither do i!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " is this about mark?", "answer": "  oh my god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " okay, it\u0092s not, it\u0092s not.", "answer": " oh my god. i cannot keep having this same fight over and over again, ross, no, you\u0092re, you\u0092re, you\u0092re making this too hard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh i\u0092m, i\u0092m making this too hard. okay, what do you want me to do.", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, i don\u0092t know. urrrgh! look, maybe we should take a break.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  hey, it\u0092s the dinosaur guy.  hi, ross.", "answer": " oh, hi chloe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " i want you to met some friends of mine.  this guy is my hero, he comes in with some stuff he wants it blown up 400%, we said we don\u0092t do that, and he says you gotta. and y'know what, we did it. and now anytime anybody wants 400, we just say \u0091let\u0092s ross it!\u0092", "answer": " and that\u0092s the only colour that comes in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " yo, chloe, do you have a quarter for the condom machine?", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " so, what are you doing here? i thought tonight was your big anniversary dinner.", "answer": " yeah, little change in plans. ahh, we\u0092re gonna break-up instead.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " oh, and i can also speak a little french. voulez-vous coucher avec moi ce soir?  why? what did i say?", "answer": " well, you just asked if i wanted to go to bed with you tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " oh my god! no wonder i get such great service at cafe maurice.", "answer": "  knock, knock, knock, knock, hi. um, could you please tell sergei that um, i was fascinated by what boutros boutros gali said in the new york times.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " you didn\u0092t say boutros boutros gali.", "answer": "  boutros boutros gali.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " he says he was too.", "answer": " interesting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": "  so i was wondering....", "answer": " okay, ah, before you get all talky again, umm, could you also please tell sergei that i really like his suit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  eh, he said, thank you very much, he thinks you look very pretty tonight, your hair, golden like the sun.  so your a chef?", "answer": " i\u0092m also thinking about opening up my own restaurant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh, really.", "answer": " monica, can i talk to you behind my menu, please.  what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " well, i was having a conversation.", "answer": " yeah but, mischa is so interested in you, that sergei and i haven\u0092t been able to say two words to each other.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " what do you want me to do? just sit here silently while you three have a conversation?", "answer": " that would be great. thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  hello!", "answer": " oh, hi. it\u0092s mark.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": "  oh.", "answer": " what? is it my breath?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " no! sorry, i just thought you were somebody else. hi!", "answer": " hi. well, look, i was just gonna leave a message, isn\u0092t tonight your, your big anniversary dinner?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " yeah. well, umm.....", "answer": " rach, are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  yeah, i\u0092m fine.", "answer": " you wanna talk, i mean i can come over?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " no! really, no, please, please, that\u0092s, that\u0092s okay.", "answer": " all right, all right, i\u0092m coming over, and i\u0092m bringing chinese food.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " oh, yeah, i\u0092m not, i\u0092m not hungry.", "answer": " it\u0092s for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " so what are you gonna do?", "answer": " what can i do? one person wants to break-up, you break-up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " hey, no way! come on, this is you guys, call her and work it out.", "answer": " oh come on, we just had this huge fight, all right, don\u0092t i have to wait a while?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " y'know that whole swimming thing is a myth.", "answer": " yeah, tell that to my uncle lenny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " why? what happened to him?", "answer": " nothing, he\u0092s just really believes in that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh, and then, we got into this big, stupid fight. i just, it was awful. i told him he treats me like a park ranger, or something, oh and then i told him i wanted to take a break, i don\u0092t want to take a break.", "answer": " wow. i\u0092m sorry. eggroll?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " no.  and then i called him, and he wasn\u0092t there.", "answer": " well, then he\u0092s, he\u0092s probably just, out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " hi! it\u0092s me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " hi! oh, i\u0092m so glad you called.", "answer": " really? i\u0092ve been thinking, this is crazy, i mean don\u0092t, don\u0092t you think we can work on this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " hey, what do you want to drink?", "answer": " who\u0092s that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " nobody.", "answer": " is it okay if i finish the apple juice?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " is that mark?", "answer": " umm, honey, look he just came over to....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " hey, dinosaur guy, look at you, so sad. come dance.", "answer": " ah, that\u0092s okay, thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " hey, you don\u0092t have to smile. you just have to dance.", "answer": " look, i don\u0092t feel like dancing, i feel like having a drink. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  and the vet said it was time. and so from half a world away, while my mother held the phone to his ear, i said good bye to my dog,. in seven languages.", "answer": " oh.  can i have a tissue?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": "  sergei, would like to apologise for my behaviour tonight.", "answer": " well, tell him, apology accepted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  oh, he\u0092s unbelievable. i mean for the first time in three years somebody wants to actually want to talk to me, but do you think he would let me enjoy that, no!!  you silly diplomat, why don\u0092t you learn some english, sergei?", "answer": " excuse me, but umm, isn\u0092t he paying for your dinner?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  i have just resigned my post. would you care to accompany me to the rainbow room? i have diplomatic coupons.", "answer": " it will be my pleasure.  my guy has diplomatic coupons. your guy can\u0092t even say coupons.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " uh,  plate?", "answer": " plate! yes, plate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " plate. plate. plate.", "answer": " see, we don\u0092t need them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": "  plate?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": "  i like this song.", "answer": " well, you\u0092re practically dancing already. why don\u0092t you just do it over here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " oh, no, no.", "answer": " what? are you married? \u0091cause that\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": "  touchet, touchet, miss americccan pie.  ameri-ccan.", "answer": " ameri-can.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " ameri-ccan.", "answer": " ameri-can. y'know it\u0092s a very hard language. let\u0092s do it again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}]